Jonathan Huynh

Location: Salt Lake City, Utah Phone: (801) 814-0351

Portfolio: https://jonvictory.github.io/tech-write-port/ Email: jonvictory@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Currently working as a technical writer focused on implementing API documentation for Workfront. 5+ years working with web technologies, responsibilities included: SEO, Technical on-page optimization, Content management, Copywriting, Marketing copywriter, and Copy editing. Motivated independent learner, currently enrolled in a Full-stack Web Development program through the University of Utah.

SKILLS

Programming: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, JSON, MySQL, Linux, Git, GitHub, GitLab, Visual Studio, Postman, REST/SOAP APIs **Writing:** APA, Microsoft Style Guide, Chicago, Madcap Flare, Salesforce, copywriting, copy editing, API Documentation, code translation, process documentation, product documentation

Web Management: Google Analytics Certified 2014, search engine optimization, content management, CMS editors, Druple, Magento, Wordpress, Foursquare

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Technical writer, Workfront Mar 2018 - Currently Employed

Technical writer in charge of scoping, planning, and implementing a completely new API Documentation system for Workfront clients, customers, and employees

Building a website that utilizes the Swagger UI and a series of Node.js packages to render JSON files containing all Workfront API objects and endpoints into HTML for the end user

Utilizing Ubuntu, Visual Studio, and GitLab to create and/or update object descriptions

Position requires constant contact with teams, departments, and individuals from all across the Workfront organization

Content copywriter, and copy editor, Clearlink Dec 2015 - Sep 2018

Managed several pools of freelance writers to generate large batches of unique content for brands that included: AT&T, CenturyLink, Comcast, Vivint, and more

Process included writing and editing content in a software specific syntax to ensure that user generated content randomized and reconstructed in a human-relatable format, which could also pass Google content-check algorithms

Gravitate Online Jul 2014 - Dec 2015

Planned, created, and managed content for over 60 Utah small business sites

Was required to be proficient at HTML/CSS, and familiar with CMS editors like Wordpress, Magento, Drupal, Foursquare, and others

EDUCATION

Utah State University, May 2014

Bachelor of Science in Economic Theory (quantitative) Minor: Mathematics GPA: 3.85

University of Utah, Feb 2020

Full-Stack Web Development Certificate - MERN Stack GPA: Certificate

Salt Lake Community College, May 2012

Associates of Science in Economics GPA: 3.9

ACHIEVEMENTS

Workfront, 2019-2020

Scoped, planned, and implementing the first API documentation project for the company

Utah State University, 2014

Received USU John M. Huntsman School of Business departmental scholarship for economics

Utah State University, 2012

Full-tuition academic scholarship for the 2012-2014 school years

Salt Lake Community College, 2012

Excellence in Diversity Academic Scholarship

Salt Lake Community College, 2011

School of business departmental scholarship for Economics